WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I REORGANIZED THE FRIDGE.
SEE? BOTTOM SHELF:
MEATS AND DAIRY.
MIDDLE SHELF: FRUITS
AND VEGETABLES
AND TOP SHELF:
EXPIRED PRODUCTS.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
BECAUSE I AM BORED
OUT OF MY MIND.
I'VE ALREADY BEEN
TO THE BANK
THE POST OFFICE
AND THE DRY CLEANERS.
DUDE, YOU JUST DESCRIBED
SEVEN DAYS' WORTH OF STUFF.
YOU GOT TO SPREAD IT OUT
A LITTLE, YOU KNOW?
HAVEN'T YOU EVER BEEN
UNEMPLOYED?
HEY, I AM NOT UNEMPLOYED.
I'M ON SABBATICAL.
HEY, DON'T GET
RELIGIOUS ON ME, OKAY?
A GUY IN YOUR POSITION
NEEDS TO BE A LITTLE BETTER
AT RELAXING
YOU KNOW?
WHY DO YOU THINK
WE HAVE
THE COMFORTABLE
CHAIRS, HUH?
COME HERE. SIT DOWN.
READY?
WATCH.
AH!
AND THEN...
OH, YEAH! HUH?
SO WHAT? WE JUST SIT?
OH, NO, NO.
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO JUST SIT.
WATCH.
( beeps )
( phone ringing )
Hello. Chandler Bing.
( high voice ):
HELLO, MR. BING.
I LOVE YOU.
Whoever this is,
stop calling me.
It's been six months.
It's not funny.
BUT I LOVE YOU.
Leave me alone.
For the love of God,
leave me alone!
AND THAT'S WEDNESDAY. AHH.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, YOU GUYS,
GUESS WHAT.
( bell clanging )
THE BRITISH ARE COMING?
OH, YOU AND YOUR WAYS.
SINCE IT'S CHRISTMASTIME,
I'M GOING TO BE
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
COLLECTING DONATIONS.
YEAH. I ALREADY HAVE
MY BELL
AND LATER ON, I GET MY BUCKET.
YEAH. YEAH.
I'M GOING TO BE OUT THERE
SPREADING JOY TO THE PEOPLE.
I MEAN, LAST YEAR,
I SPREAD A LITTLE JOY
BUT NOT REALLY ENOUGH
SO THIS YEAR, I'M GOING
TO DO THE WHOLE CITY.
YOU KNOW, I KNEW
A GIRL IN HIGH SCHOOL
THAT DID THAT.
SHE WAS VERY POPULAR.
SO, PHEEBS, WHERE ARE YOU
DOING ALL YOUR BELL RINGING?
THEY GAVE ME A GREAT SPOT
RIGHT BY MACY'S.
YEAH, THEY HARDLY EVER GIVE
SUCH A GOOD CORNER TO A ROOKIE
BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN SAY "MERRY CHRISTMAS"
IN 25 LANGUAGES.
I LIED.
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, YOU GUYS,
HERE'S DANNY. WATCH.
JUST WATCH THIS.
SEE?
STILL PRETENDING
HE'S NOT INTERESTED.
OKAY, HE'S COMING OVER.
JUST PRETEND
LIKE WE DON'T KNOW HIM.
WE'VE FORGOTTEN WHO HE IS.
HEY, GUYS.
All:
HEY, DANNY.
OH, DANNY, HEY.
WHEN DID YOU
GET HERE?
OH, GOD.
DANNY, YOU KNOW RACHEL.
SHE'S NICE.
SHE'S NOT BAD
TO LOOK AT, RIGHT?
THANKS, MON.
WELL, OF COURSE.
DO YOU WANT TO GO OUT
ON A DATE WITH HER?
MONICA!
ABSOLUTELY.
IS FRIDAY OKAY?
FRIDAY IS PERFECT.
SHE CAN'T WAIT.
ON THE DATE,
I WILL BE ABLE
TO TALK TO HER
DIRECTLY, RIGHT?
OKAY, WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T ANSWER ME.
I HAVE A DATE WITH DANNY.
HOW COULD I NOT
GET THE PART?
THE PLAY WAS ABOUT
A 29-YEAR-OLD
ITALIAN ACTOR
FROM QUEENS.
WELL, TALIA SHIRE SUDDENLY
BECAME AVAILABLE.
SHE'S A WOMAN.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
SHE NAILED IT.
OKAY. IS THERE
ANYTHING ELSE?
WELL, YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO SAY NO AGAIN
BUT GAY PORN?
HAPPY HOLIDAYS!
FELIZ NAVIDAD!
ALLO AND MERRY CHRISTMAS.
OH, THANK YOU, SIR.
HERE'S SOME JOY.
PHOEBE!
HEY!
I JUST WANTED TO SEE
HOW IT'S GOING.
WELL, IT'S GOING OKAY.
WELL, GOOD.
HERE, LET ME HELP YOU OUT.
OH, THANKS.
YEAH.
WOW.
IS THAT A NEW
SUEDE JACKET?
IT LOOKS REALLY EXPENSIVE.
YEAH... I GUESS.
JUST GET YOUR NAILS DONE?
YES, PHOEBE, BUT THIS IS
ALL I HAVE, OKAY?
OKAY. THANKS.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
HERE'S YOUR JOY.
THANK YOU.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
WAIT. YOU CAN'T TAKE
THE MONEY OUT.
I'M MAKING CHANGE.
I NEED CHANGE FOR THE BUS.
BUT CAN'T YOU LEAVE THE DOLLAR?
THIS MONEY'S FOR THE POOR.
I'M POOR. I GOT
TO TAKE THE BUS.
OKAY. SEASON'S GREETINGS
AND EVERYTHING, BUT STILL...
BITE ME, BLONDIE.
OH!
WOW.
OH, I'M GOING TO GIVE HIM
SOMETHING BESIDES JOY.
JUST...
THAT PART WAS
PERFECT FOR ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T GET IT.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU SHOULD DO?
YOU SHOULD MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN
FOR YOURSELF, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, LIKE WRITE A PLAY.
WRITE A MOVIE, HUH?
WHAT ABOUT THOSE
GOOD WILL HUNTING GUYS?
COME ON, ROSS
BE REALISTIC, YOU KNOW?
IF I DID WRITE SOMETHING
WHAT ARE THE CHANCES I COULD GET
THOSE GUYS TO STAR IN IT?
WAIT A SECOND.
I COULD STAR IN IT.
OR THAT.
I CAN'T WRITE, YOU KNOW.
I'M AN ACTOR.
I DON'T HAVE THE DISCIPLINE
THAT IT TAKES, YOU KNOW?
I CAN'T DO IT.
I'LL HELP YOU.
YEAH. I'LL MAKE
UP A SCHEDULE
AND MAKE SURE
YOU STICK TO IT.
PLUS IT WILL GIVE ME
SOMETHING TO DO.
YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
YEAH.
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT. WE'LL
START OFF SLOW.
THE ONLY THING YOU HAVE
TO DO TONIGHT
IS COME UP WITH THE NAME
OF YOUR MAIN CHARACTER.
DONE.
AND IT CAN'T BE JOEY.
IT'S NOT.
OR JOSEPH.
OH.
HI.
WHAT'S UP?
I JUST SAW DANNY GETTING
ON THE SUBWAY WITH A GIRL
AND HE HAD HIS ARM
AROUND HER.
I'M SORRY.
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
YOU MEDDLED
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
YOU HAD NO RELATIONSHIP.
NO, BUT I WAS
DOING MY THING
AND EVERYTHING WAS
GOING ACCORDING TO THE PLAN.
OH, GOD, STOP WITH THE PLAN.
SO WHAT? SO WHAT IF YOU SAW
HIM WITH A GIRL.
WHO CARES? IT DOESN'T
MEAN ANYTHING.
LOOK, YOU'RE GOING
TO GO OUT ON A
DATE WITH DANNY
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO BE SO CHARMING
HE'S GOING TO FORGET ABOUT
THAT STUPID SUBWAY GIRL.
SHE WAS KIND OF STUPID.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. I'M JUST GOING
TO GO ON THE DATE.
I'M JUST GOING
THAT IS THE NEW PLAN.
HURRY! HURRY!
HEY, HOW DO YOU SPELL
SUSPICIOUS?
WHY?
BECAUSE I THINK
THIS CHARACTER IS GOING
TO BE SUSPICIOUS ABOUT STUFF.
YES!
CHANDLER BING, SEVEN,
CHANDLER BING, ZERO.
YOU'RE DRIVING
ME CRAZY WITH THAT.
OKAY. I'LL STOP.
DON'T STOP.
MOVE THE BALL FURTHER AWAY.
ROSS COULD MAKE THAT SHOT.
WELL, YOU SUCK, BUT AT LEAST
YOU SUCK AT A MAN'S GAME NOW.
YOU WANT TO PLAY?
CHANDLER, I CAN'T BE
PLAYING GAMES.
ROSS IS GOING
TO BE HOME SOON
AND I HAVE TO WRITE
FIVE WHOLE PAGES
IF I'M GOING TO STICK
TO HIS SCHEDULE.
PLAY FOR THE NEXT 30 MINUTES
AND YOU CAN WRITE
UNTIL HE GETS HOME.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT LISTEN,
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE CRANK IT
UP A NOTCH?
I'M INTRIGUED.
ALL RIGHT. ALL WE NEED
IS A LITTLE LIGHTER FLUID.
OKAY, BUT BE
CAREFUL, OKAY?
BECAUSE I WANT TO GET
OUR SECURITY DEPOSIT BACK.
YEAH, I THINK
WE SAID GOOD-BYE TO THAT
WHEN WE INVENTED HAMMER DARTS.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
DO YOU REMEMBER WHICH PART
IS NOT SPACKLED?
YEAH, RIGHT HERE.
OH, THANK YOU.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
NO, THAT'S TRASH,
YOUNG LADY.
NO. YOU CAN'T...
HEY, STOP THAT YOUNG LADY!
SHE DONATED TRASH!
HEY!
THE CHARITY'S ON FIRE!
HELP! OH, GOOD.
THANK YOU. I NEED THAT.
WOO! WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S 9:00 IN THE MORNING.
ALL RIGHT.
"A ROOM.
"A MAN ENTERS.
HE LOOKS SUSPICIOUS."
THAT'S IT?
JOEY, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO HAVE
FIVE PAGES DONE BY NOW
INCLUDING AN EXCITING INCIDENT.
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
"THE OFFICIAL RULE BOOK
OF FIREBALL."
YEAH, THAT'S THE GAME
WE WERE PLAYING.
OH, YEAH, GREAT. SEE,
YOU TAKE A TENNIS BALL
A BOWL AND LIGHTER FLUID...
OOPS.
THIS IS HELPING
YOUR CAREER?
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED
TO BE AN ACTOR.
NOT THE CREATOR
OF "CRAZY LAWSUIT GAME."
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'LL GET BACK
TO WORK.
AND SHAME ON YOU.
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER.
JOEY NEEDS TO WORK.
NOW, COME ON.
HEY.
UH-UH. YOU CAN HAVE
THIS BACK
WHEN THE FIVE PAGES
ARE DONE, HUH?
AH!
I HAD A REALLY NICE TIME
TONIGHT.
SO DID I.
I'M REALLY GLAD
MONICA ASKED US OUT.
I'D LOVE TO ASK
YOU IN, BUT, UH...
MY SISTER'S VISITING
AND I THINK SHE'S ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
YOUR SISTER?
YOUR SISTER'S ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH?
OH, I SAW YOU WITH HER
ON THE SUBWAY
AND NOW SHE'S ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH.
OH, GOD!
OH, I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU.
HEY, GREAT, YOU'RE UP.
RACHEL, THIS IS MY SISTER,
KRISTA.
KRISTA, THIS IS RACHEL.
HI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I WISH YOU TOLD ME
WE WERE HAVING COMPANY.
I'D HAVE FIXED
MYSELF UP.
LIKE IT WOULD HELP.
YOU ARE SO BAD.
YOU ARE.
YOU ARE!
YOU ARE SO DEAD.
I'M GOING TO GET YOU.
( squeals )
COME HERE!
( both laughing )
UM, VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
NOBODY... NOBODY
RESPECTS THE BUCKET.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
WHAT PEOPLE PUT IN HERE.
OKAY. DOES THIS LOOK
LIKE A GARBAGE CAN TO YOU?
NO.
DOES IT LOOK LIKE AN ASHTRAY?
DOES IT LOOK LIKE A URINAL?
EWW!
PHEEBS, YOU GOING
TO GO BACK OUT THERE?
WELL, YEAH.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE
ANY MORE CRAP, OKAY?
NO MORE MRS. NICE BUCKET.
GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU'RE TOUGH.
YOU LIVED
ON THE STREET.
I'M GOING TO GO BACK
TO BEING STREET PHOEBE.
YEAH.
OH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
I CAN'T GO TOTALLY BACK
BECAUSE STREET PHOEBE
REALLY WOULDN'T BE FRIENDS
WITH YOU GUYS.
HI. UM, CAN I ASK
YOU GUYS SOMETHING?
Both:
SURE.
UM, I DON'T HAVE
ANY BROTHERS,
SO I DON'T KNOW
BUT DID YOU GUYS WRESTLE?
OH, YEAH.
ALL THE TIME.
IN FACT, I WAS
UNDEFEATED.
WELL, YOU WEIGHED 200 POUNDS.
STILL, I WAS
QUICK AS A CAT.
WELL, I MET DANNY'S SISTER
YESTERDAY--
UH, THAT WAS ACTUALLY
THE GIRL ON THE SUBWAY--
AND, UH, YEAH,
THEY WERE VERY, YOU KNOW...
WRESTLE-Y...
BUT I GUESS THAT'S NORMAL?
WE DON'T... WE
DON'T WRESTLE NOW.
NOT SINCE I GOT TOO STRONG
FOR YOU.
TOO STRONG FOR ME?
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO
GO RIGHT NOW?
'CAUSE I'LL TAKE YOU
RIGHT NOW, BUDDY.
YOU WANT TO GO?
OH, FINE.
READY?
WRESTLE.
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
UM, ACTUALLY,
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT HELPS A
LOT. THANKS.
GUYS, COME ON. LET'S GO.
THE PUCK DROPS IN 20 MINUTES.
JOEY'S NOT GOING.
I DIDN'T FINISH
MY FIVE PAGES.
WELL, WHY CAN'T YOU
FINISH THEM TOMORROW?
BECAUSE TOMORROW
HE'S REDOING YESTERDAY'S PAGES.
AND YESTERDAY'S PAGES
DID NOT REFLECT MY BEST WORK.
WHY DON'T YOU CUT HIM
A LITTLE SLACK, OKAY?
MAYBE IF HE RELAXES A LITTLE
BIT, HE'LL GET SOME WORK DONE.
I THINK HE'S BEEN
RELAXING ENOUGH
THANKS TO YOU
AND FIREBALL.
DUDE, IF YOU THINK
FIREBALL'S RELAXING
YOU OBVIOUSLY HAVE NEVER PLAYED.
THE ONLY REASON
YOU ARE DOING THIS TO JOEY
IS BECAUSE YOU ARE BORED, OKAY?
IT'S NOT HIS FAULT
YOU'RE UNEMPLOYED.
I AM NOT UNEMPLOYED.
I'M ON SABBATICAL.
COME ON, LOOK, GUYS.
DON'T FIGHT.
AND THE REASON I'M DOING THIS
IS BECAUSE I AM JOEY'S FRIEND
AND IF YOU WERE A GOOD FRIEND,
YOU'D BE DOING THE SAME THING.
SO BEING A GOOD
FRIEND MEANS ACTING
LIKE A TOTAL JERK.
IF IT DOES, THEN YOU'RE
AN AMAZING FRIEND OF MINE.
Joey:
HEY, GUYS, HEY.
HOW ABOUT WE SETTLE THIS
OVER A FRIENDLY
GAME OF FIREBALL? HUH?
I'LL GO UNHOOK THE
SMOKE DETECTORS.
HOW ABOUT WE SETTLE THIS
RIGHT NOW?
( gasps )
THERE. NOW NO ONE'S GOING
TO THE GAME.
I PAID FOR THOSE TICKETS.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
YOU SAID YOU WOULD,
BUT YOU NEVER DID.
OH, YEAH.
( goofy laughing )
SO, WE FINALLY GET
TO THE TOP OF THE MOUNTAIN
AND AIRHEAD HERE
FORGETS THE CAMERA.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT
SAME THING HAPPENED
TO ME ONE TIME.
WHEN DID THAT
HAPPEN TO YOU?
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
WE WERE JOGGING
IN THE PARK
WE SAW THAT
REALLY PRETTY BIRD
AND I WANTED
TO TAKE A PICTURE
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE
MY CAMERA.
OKAY. FIRST OF ALL,
CHASING THE CHURRO
GUY IS NOT JOGGING.
OH, THIS IS SO GOOD.
YOU HAVE GOT TO TRY IT.
THAT IS GOOD.
OH. DAMN.
I GOT IT ON MY PANTS.
HERE. I'LL GET IT.
WE BETTER TAKE
THESE OFF UPSTAIRS
OR THAT STAIN'S
GOING TO SET.
I WANT TO WEAR THESE PANTS
ON OUR DATE TONIGHT.
OH, GREAT.
OKAY. BYE.
OH, MY GOD...
THAT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
OKAY, SEE? I TOLD YOU.
YEAH, WOW... SORRY, RACH.
I DON'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE BROTHER AND SISTER.
THEY'RE BROTHER AND SISTER?!
( bell ringing )
OH! WAIT A MINUTE.
OPEN YOUR HAND.
LET ME TAKE A LOOK.
QUARTER, DIME, LINT.
NOT INTERESTED IN THAT.
WHAT'S THIS,
A CANADIAN COIN?
GET OUT OF HERE!
OH, MY GOSH.
WHOA! NO DRINKS
NEAR THE BUCKET.
SET IT DOWN OVER THERE
AND THEN YOU CAN
MAKE A CONTRIBUTION.
AND YOU LEAVE THE
"HURT BUNNY" LOOK
OVER THERE, TOO.
OH, HI, BOB.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO GET OUT OF HERE!
UH, PHOEBE,
WE'VE BEEN GETTING COMPLAINTS
AND, UH, WE'RE GOING TO MOVE YOU
TO A LESS HIGH-PROFILE SPOT.
WHAT?
UH, GINGER'S GOING TO
TAKE OVER THIS CORNER.
THAT CHICK CAN'T
HANDLE MY CORNER.
LOOK, EITHER YOU
LEAVE OR WE REMOVE YOU.
FINE.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL
GIVE YOU ONE POINTER.
LOOK AT FOR THAT BITCH.
( knocking )
OH. HI, RACH.
I THOUGHT WE SAID 7:00.
YEAH. YOU KNOW WHAT?
UH, LET'S SKIP IT.
WHAT? WHY?
UM... YOU AND YOUR
SISTER SEEM TO HAVE
A VERY SPECIAL BOND.
OH, GREAT.
THAT SPECIAL BOND AGAIN.
WHY DO WOMEN HAVE
SUCH A PROBLEM
WITH THE FACT
THAT I'M CLOSE
WITH MY SISTER?
WELL... OKAY, LOOK.
LISTEN... I DON'T
KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE, BUT...
DO YOU HAVE BROTHERS?
NO. I HAVE TWO SISTERS.
ONE OF THEM ACTUALLY HAS
A VERY MASCULINE ENERGY.
ARE YOU CLOSE WITH THEM?
NO, NO. THEY'RE NOT
VERY NICE PEOPLE.
COME HERE.
LISTEN. I REALLY
LIKE YOU, OKAY?
I THINK THIS COULD
GO SOMEWHERE.
SO WHAT IF I'M CLOSE
TO MY FAMILY?
YOU GOING TO LET THAT
STAND IN THE WAY OF US?
WELL... I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT
WAY, YOU KNOW...
DANNY, HURRY UP.
THE BATH'S GETTING COLD.
WHAT?
YEAH. I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OH, HEY. THERE'S
SOME KIDS PLAYING
IN THE STREET.
YOU WANT TO
GO DOWN THERE
GIVE THEM A PROJECT,
RUIN THEIR DAY?
HEY, IF THEY HAVE A BALL
MAYBE YOU COULD STICK
RAZOR BLADES IN IT
AND TEACH THEM A NEW GAME--
"GOING TO NEED STITCHES" BALL.
HEY, GUYS. I WAS
AT THE LIBRARY ALL MORNING
AND I ALREADY
FINISHED MY FIVE
PAGES FOR TODAY.
GREAT. NOW WE CAN
GO TO THE RANGER
GAME LAST NIGHT.
NO, DUDE.
ROSS TORE UP THE TICKETS.
I GUESS WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
SO MANY DISTRACTIONS
IT'S EASIER FOR YOU
TO FOCUS, HUH?
YEAH, OR ALSO,
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE SOMEBODY
BREATHING DOWN YOUR NECK
ALL THE LIVELONG DAY!
WELL... THAT'S FINE,
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING IS
I FINISHED IT
AND I THINK IT'S REALLY GOOD
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT WOULD REALLY HELP ME
IS IF I COULD HEAR IT, SO
WOULD YOU GUYS READ IT FOR ME?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
IT'S A TYPICAL NEW
YORK CITY APARTMENT--
TWO GUYS ARE
HANGING OUT. ROSS?
HEY, MAN.
WHAT IS UP?
ABOUT YESTERDAY,
I WAS REALLY WRONG.
I AM SORRY.
NO, IT WAS ME. I'M
SORRY. I OVERREACTED.
MAYBE IT WAS BOTH OF US
BUT WE HAD
OUR BEST FRIEND'S INTER...
BUT WE HAD OUR BEST FRIEND'S
INTEREST AT HEART.
COULD I BE MORE SORRY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I AM ONE SORRY...
POLONTOLOGIST...
ALL RIGHT, JOEY.
WE-WE GET IT.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, TOO.
OH, NO. NO, NO. KEEP READING.
THE GOOD PART'S COMING UP.
KEEP GOING.
I AM SORRY, CHANDLER.
I AM SORRY, ROSS.
A HANDSOME
MAN ENTERS.
HEY... HOW'S IT
GOING, GUYS?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU TWO ARE
TALKING ABOUT
BUT I WOULD JUST
LIKE TO SAY THANKS
TO BOTH OF YOU.
YOU-- YOU WOULDN'T LET
ME GIVE UP ON MYSELF
AND YOU-- WELL, YOU
CO-CREATED FIREBALL.
THE END.
THIS TOOK YOU ALL DAY?
NO, NO. THIS ONLY
TOOK FIVE MINUTES.
I SPENT THE
REST OF THE DAY
COMING UP WITH NEW,
ULTIMATE FIREBALL.
( crazed laughing )
IT'S A TYPICAL
NEW YORK CITY APARTMENT.
TWO GIRLS ARE JUST HANGING OUT.
HI. HOW'RE YOU
DOING, KELLY?
I'M DOING JUST FINE.
GOD, TIFFANY,
YOU SMELL SO GREAT.
IT'S MY NEW PERFUME.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME CLOSER
WHERE YOU CAN REALLY
APPRECIATE IT?
OH, YOU KNOW, JOEY,
YOU ARE SICK.
THIS IS DISGUSTING.
I'M NOT READING THIS.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. THE HANDSOME
MAN WAS ABOUT TO ENTER!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]